[ © anoXmous
@ https://thepiratebay.sx/user/[qusawa]
[Birds Twittering]
[Vehicle Passing]
♪♪ [Acoustic Guitar]
[Girl] I don't feel anything.
[Girl #2]
Come on. It's graduation.
Did you see what
Mr. Carroll wrote
in my yearbook?
Well, he ridiculed me
all year long,
and then he writes,
"You're a real live wire.
Love, Mr. Carroll."
You know, it's all so phony.
[Boy] Hmm.
He wants to leave things
on a good note.
Well, when Mr. Carroll
uses the word "love,"
I look for a new word.
Lloyd,
she's being difficult.
- I'm gonna take out Diane Court again.
- That's unlikely.
Is the movies
a good second date,
you know, as a date?
- But you never had a first date.
- Yes, I did.
I sat across from her at a mall.
We ate together. That's eating.
- Sharing an important physical event.
- That's not even a scam.
- What's a scam?
- Going out as friends.
No, it's not. Scam is lusting.
[Together]
Then what's a date?
A date is prearrangement,
with a possibility for love.
[Girl #1]
Then what's love?
I'm gonna call her.
Diane Court doesn't go out
with guys like you. She's a brain.
Trapped in the body
of a game-show hostess.
[Girl #1]
Diane Court does not realize
how good looking she is.
This sounds great to me. I'm gonna call her.
That's what's cool about her.
Brains stay with brains.
The bomb could go off, and their mutant genes
would form the same cliques.
I wouldn't get my hopes up, Lloyd.
I'm sorry.
It’s just you're a really nice guy,
and we don't want you to get hurt.
I wanna get hurt!
"Well, it's almost over.
We've gone to school together for three years."
I might cut that part.
Why? That's fine.
Ah, it's nice.
[Man]
♪ This may come
as a shocking surprise ♪
♪ I have to take a walk
I have to kiss it good-bye ♪
[Timer Beeping]
♪ Good-bye, my love ♪
♪ Ah, good-bye, my love ♪
♪ Not another time ♪
♪ Ah, good-bye, my lo— ♪
[Slowing, Fluctuating]
♪♪ [Resumes Normal Speed:
Continues, Indistinct]
"Having taken a few courses
at the university this year,
"I have glimpsed our future,
and all I can say is...
go back."
[Laughs]
"Go back." What a great line.
You like it?
Oh, yeah!
- I didn't think anyone would get it.
- Oh, no, no.
It's-It's wonderful. It's-
Yeah?
No, don't worry about it.
You're very funny.
"Go back." That's great.
All right. No more.
I'm gonna save it.
[Laughs] Okay.
[Off-key]
♪ I decided long ago ♪
♪ Never to walk in anyone's shadow ♪
♪ If I fail, if I succeed ♪
♪ At least I lived as I believed ♪
♪ No matter what they take from me ♪
♪ They can't take away ♪
Wow!
♪ My dignity ♪
♪ Because the greatest ♪
♪ Love of all is happening to me ♪
[Cheering, Whooping]
♪ I found ♪
Yeah!
♪ The greatest ♪
♪ Love of all inside of me ♪♪
[Cheering]
I love you guys.
Thanks, bro.
Party at Vahlere's.
There's gonna be eight kegs.
See you there.
[Boys] Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe,
Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe!
Thank you, Joe.
[Feedback Squeals]
Thank you.
Thank you, Joe.
And now it's time.
I just can't introduce
this person without saying...
history, oceanography,
creative writing...
biochemistry.
I think you know
who I'm talking about.
We're going to remember
this student who said,
"Hey, world, check me out."
Giving a speech entitled...
"Soaring Ahead,"
Miss Diane Court.
Thank you.
- The real world.
- Look at those eyes.
We're all about to enter
the real world.
That's what everybody says.
But most of us have been in
the real world a long time.
But I have something
to tell everybody.
I've glimpsed our future,
and all I can say is... go back.
[Diane's Father Laughing]
Well, it's almost over.
Uh, we've gone to school
together for three years,
and we've been through a lot.
But with that training net
of high school gone,
what's going to happen to us?
We all know what the answers are.
We want to be happy,
go to college, work hard,
maybe raise a family.
But what if that doesn't happen?
I have to be honest though.
I have-
I have all the hope
and ambition in the world.
But when I think about the future,
the truth is...
I am...
really...
scared.
All right.
Get up on it.
[Camera Shutter Clicks]
Yea! All right.
Hey, yea!
[Woman]
I'll see you at home.
All right.
- Now, do yourself
and everyone who loves you a favor-
- All right, Mom.
and don't talk to Joe.
Mom, Mom-
Stop. Okay?
Bye.
See you later,
Mrs. Flood.
Bye.
Bye, Mrs. Flood.
All right.
Look at those eyes.
Lloyd, give it up.
Do me a favor.
Take a picture of me with her.
Lloyd-
Just do it. Please?
That’s just
so embarrassing.
Please?
All right.
Just do it.
All right. Okay.
Sure. It's your life.
Wait for me when I get around her.
[Muttering] ...together.
All right, man. I got it.
Your graduation present
is parked right over there.
Are you kidding? That?
[Camera Shutter Clicks]
Lloyd? I'm sorry.
Hey, Sis.
Sam had me do a new crown,
we had two root canals to do,
and Jason has a sore throat.
Your big graduation,
and no one was there.
Hey, it's no problem.
I called Mom and Dad in Germany.
It's like they were there.
- I hope you understand.
- Hey, bad throat, huh, J-man?
- [Weakly] Yeah.
- Yeah, he's not at full "Yeah!" strength.
[Sighs]
Poor little man.
[Glass Clinking]
Why do you eat that stuff?
There's no food in your food.
- ♪♪ [Rock, Volume Increases]
- Not too loud. The red line's there for a reason.
How do you know how to draw
the red line anyway?
Because it's loud enough,
and the neighbors don't complain.
That's how come I know.
Good thing there's not
a red line on you, J-man. Yeah!
[Loudly]
Yeah!
He's back!
Hey, my brother,
can I borrow a copy
of your Hey Soul Classics?
No, my brother.
You have to go buy your own.
Hook you off the jab.
Hook up the jab.
Why can't you be his uncle
and not his playmate?
[Quietly]
Jesus Christ.
- What?
- Get in a good mood.
How hard is it just to decide to be in a good mood,
and then be in a good mood?
Gee, it's easy.
Okay, I'm sorry that Mom and Dad
made you take me in. Really.
If it's such a big deal, I'll go.
But remember this. You used to be fun.
You used to be warped
and twisted and hilarious.
And I mean that in the best way.
I mean it as a compliment.
I mean, I'm sorry...
that T-I-M left you.
But I am not T-I-M!
- I was hilarious once, wasn't I?
- Yeah.
I still am.
Dad, you have to teach me
the stick shift this weekend.
Okay, promise. Now, just don't go upstairs yet.
Come here a minute.
I want to show you something.
[Lock Turning]
What are you doing?
Well, since I'm not only your father,
I'm also your friend,
I had to get you
two presents.
Oh, God!
This is ridiculous!
Now, this is the only thing
your mother ever gave me
that I kept.
Now it's yours.
Well, go ahead.
Open it now.
Oh, God! I don't need all these presents.
I don't know any kid who got a car. I mean, it's-
Oh, God.
Wow. It's beautiful.
They really applauded you today, honey.
I was standing up there
and looking at all the people,
and I felt like they didn't know me.
[Sighs]
I mean, maybe I shouldn't
have taken all those courses
off-school, 'cause...
everybody thinks I-
- Forget it.
- No, wait a minute.
Everybody thinks you're what?
Everybody thinks I'm a priss.
Diane, in a million years
you could never be a priss.
[Laughs]
It's all working out for you, honey.
Do you see?
It's working out
just like we planned.
All the— All the years, the summer schools,
all the vacations you gave up.
It's all working out
just like we planned.
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
[Chuckles]
Sorry.
I love you, Dad.
I love you too, honey.
♪♪ [Rock On Boom Box]
[Grunting]
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on, hah!
Boom!
Hyah!
[Grunting Continues]
Come on, J-man. Come on.
Get the bag. Come on.
Yaah!
An exciting kick.
My brother, let's go.
Yaah, yaah, yaah!
Put the gloves down.
You're headed
for day care, buddy.
Be tough, J-man.
He's a mess!
I'll be in my office.
I just washed this shirt, didn't I?
Yeah!
Please, not in my ear.
Not in my ear.
[Punching Keypad]
[Line Ringing]
-Jim Court.
- Hello. May I please speak
with Diane, please?
Uh, sorry, Diane isn't here
at the moment.
Oh. Uh, okay. Um-
This the guy
with the Mustang?
- No.
- The guy with the Datsun?
No.
- Uh, the truck?
- No, not-not really.
Uh, no, actually, basically,
uh, you don't know me. I'm-
I'm a friend of your daughter's.
Well, I sat with her yesterday at a mall.
Um, I drive
a blue Chevy Malibu if you-
Oh.
I guess I'm pretty bad at this,
but what I want to do is-
Could I please-
Why don't I get
a phone number from you?
That's usually how it works.
Oh. Okay.
Uh, Lloyd Dobler.
555-1342.
That's 555-1342.
Okay.
I'll get her the message.
Okay. She's pretty great,
isn't she?
What?
- She's really pretty great, isn't she?
- Yeah, she is.
Good luck, kid.
Good afternoon.
Okay, bye.
[Ringing]
Jim Court.
No, this is her father.
Can I take-
What?
No, I didn't get the letter.
Yes!
Yes, right away.
Ye— Thank you. Good-bye.
♪♪ [Stereo: Jazz Rock]
[Singing Along]
♪ Rikki, don't lose that number♪
♪ You don't want to call nobody else ♪
♪♪ [Hums]
♪ Send it off in a letter to yourself♪
♪ Rikki, don't lose that number♪
♪ It's the only one you own ♪♪
[Chuckles]
Oh, Mr. Taylor,
you're a vision in green.
Here, let me mail this for you.
Thank you.
Yeah, you can trust a man
who writes a letter every day.
Is Diane here?
I gotta talk with her.
She's upstairs, Mr. Court.
Okay.
I gotta tell you this carefully.
Oh, Lee, Ben,
could you do me a favor?
Just a couple minutes.
Yes, sir, Mr. Court.
Great.
Won't be long. Thanks.
[Chattering]
What?
I just had a phone call.
Tell me.
Is it bad news?
No, just listen.
You won the Reed Fellowship.
Are you kidding?
You're not kidding?
You're not kidding!
You won it.
You're gonna study at
the finest institute in England.
The toughest
fellowship in the country, and you won it.
I won?
You're gonna take a big step,
a big leap, and before you do,
I just want one thing
from you, miss.
You stand up straight
and admit you're special.
God.
I'll have to go on a plane.
Worry about that later!
Now, come on.
Tell me that you're special!
Don't do this to me.
You're too good at making me nervous.
No, listen to me!
You're the best
in the country.
Don't you understand?
It's like... a pyramid.
It starts out with everybody,
and it narrows through your life
and through everything.
And all the hoopla
and the competition narrows it
down to one brilliant person...
who is so special they
celebrate you on two continents.
And it's you.
So tell me something.
Where's the flaw in that?
There is no flaw. Huh?
[Laughs]
[Sobs]
Hello?
Ah, yeah.
Just a second, Corey.
Oh, sorry.
[Quietly]
Diane Court.
Don't-Don't go in there!
Forget it! Forget it!
It's mine, it's mine!
[Door Slams]
[Sister]
Too bad!
No noise, no sound, no movement.
Nothing.
Hello. Diane?
Hi. You called me?
Yeah, I read about
your fellowship in the paper.
I'm very glad you called me back.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I just wanted to
congratulate you on that
scholarship to England,
and I wanted to just tell you
I thought your speech
was really incredible.
Thank you very much.
Whoa, what a day, huh?
Yeah, what a day.
- Yeah.
Quick question.
Do-Do you know who I am?
Yes, we sat together
at Bell Square.
Yeah, yeah. You remember.
No, I read it
on the message.
- Okay, um, so it's Lloyd,
and, um, uh, let's go out.
- [Chuckles]
You wanna go out?
Oh, thanks, but I'm busy.
Busy.
Yes.
Things are hectic now,
but thanks.
You busy on Friday?
Yeah.
I have to help my father.
Are you busy on Saturday?
Saturday I have some things
to do around the house.
[Vehicle Horn Honks In Distance]
So you're— So you're...
monumentally busy?
Well, not monumentally.
What about tonight then?
You gonna go to
that party at Vahlere's?
Mmm-
I can't allow you to leave
the country without attending
Vahlere's graduation event.
This gentleman is- He's 22,
and he comes out of hiding,
like, once a year for this occasion.
He dresses up as
the Lakeside Rooster,
and he makes this drink
called the Purple Passion.
- Actually, I think that, uh-
- You're not in England yet.
You know that, of course.
By the way,
I lived in England
for three months.
My parents are in the army,
so we lived in England
and Germany.
I could give you
an enormous amount of tips—
many tips, English tips.
Well-
- No tips. I won't give
any tips of any kind.
- I'll go.
- Pardon me?
You will?
Excellent! All right.
This is great.
- You will? Really?
- I'll go.
All right. This is really great.
All right. We're goin' out.
It's a date. It's a scam.
Whatever, whatever. All right.
I'll pick you up at, what, 8:00?
- 8:00.
- [Whispers]
8:00.
- Good-bye.
[Handset Slams In Cradle]
Lloyd Dobler.
Thank you, little man.
♪♪ [Imitates Electric Guitar]
Now work that bag!
Work that bag, J-man!
Left hook!
Hook off the jab!
Straight left hand.
What do we love?
Pain!
Work that jab!
Work that hook! Work that hook!
Okay, take a break, take a break.
[Jim]
Be right there.
Hi. Lloyd Dobler, sir.
How are you?
Pleasure to meet you.
Hello, Lloyd.
Hello. Heard about
the graduation present.
Really quite a car.
Look, I know you're busy.
You don't have to entertain me,
but, uh, you can trust me.
I'll tell you about myself.
I'm 19, been overseas for
a couple semesters. Now I'm back.
I'm an athlete, so I rarely drink.
Ever heard of kickboxing,
sport of the future?
Don "The Dragon" Wilson?
Benny "The Jet" Urquidez?
Murray Smith?
Champions of the sport?
I can see by your face, no.
My point is, you can relax.
Your daughter will be safe
with me for the next
seven to eight hours, sir.
Fine, Lloyd.
Come in.
Thank you.
How you doin'?
Okay, fine.
Is she around?
Yeah. Uh, honey?
[Quietly]
Whoa.
- Hi.
- [Whispers]
Hi.
[Kisses]
Would you hold this for me?
Yeah.
[Door Creaks Loudly]
What are these?
Uh, Bavarian
Dutch-style pretzels.
Oh.
Um, would it be terrible
if I wanted to go home early?
No.
[Man On Stereo, Loud]
♪ Oh, sex bomb exploding ♪
♪♪ [Turns Off]
[Dog Barking In Distance]
[Engine Starts]
♪♪ [Rock On Stereo]
[Chattering]
Hi!
Oh, my God.
[Laughing]
[Girl]
Hi, Lloyd!
You okay?
Uh-huh.
Want a drink?
[Boy]
What's up, Lloyd?
Hey!
[Indistinct]
[Girl] Hey, Dobler!
[Girl #2]
We are out of control!
Dude, that's not happening.
I gotta go to summer school,
if you can believe that.
Dude, I know what—
[Continues, Indistinct]
[Boy]
Hey, Lloyd!
Hi, Lloyd.
How you doin'?
It's gotta stay purple
all night.
[Chuckles] Lloyd, buddy!
How you doin'?
You know Diane Court?
Wow, Diane. Well—
Listen, man, I need you
to be the key master.
I was just-
A very responsible young man
you're out with tonight.
Thanks a lot, Lloyd.
I was just gonna
kind of move around.
Thanks.
Key master?
Yeah. I have to judge
who can drive home
and who can't.
I gotta keep their keys.
So it's an honor.
No.
[Grunts]
We finally graduated,
big dude guy!
All right!
I'm so glad you came to this.
I've always wanted you
to come to one of these.
Here's my keys!
[Chuckling Scream]
I wish you had
done that without
your keys in your hand!
Come with me. There are so many
cute guys here. Come on.
[Lloyd] Let go of me!
I love you, man!
I love you too!
[Screams]
Homeboy.
Hey!
Mike Cameron.
How you doin'?
What?
Mike Cameron.
This is one fresh jam, huh?
Yeah!
Yeah. Hey—
Oh, God, listen.
I- I don't know you very well,
you know, but I wanted to ask you.
- How'd you get Diane Court to go out with you?
- I called her up.
But how come it worked?
I mean, like, what are you?
I'm Lloyd Dobler.
This is great.
This gives me hope. Thanks.
All right. Key?
I wrote 63 songs this year.
They're all about Joe,
and I'm going to play every
single one of them tonight.
I just saw Joe. He's here.
Well, you don't have to be
so dramatic about it.
You did try and kill yourself
because of the guy.
What was it like
after it happened, Corey?
I've always wanted to know.
She explained it all
on Wake Up, Seattle.
Where were you?
Stop! I am fine now.
I'm all right.
All everybody does
is ask me about this,
and I'm fine.
Did Joe come
with Mimi tonight?
Keys. Keys, anybody?
All right, key master.
All right.
Hey, man.
Hey, how you doin'?
Good.
Lloyd!
Lloyd Dobler, I got you.
How you doing, Miss Evans?
You missed every one of your
career-counseling sessions.
Call me obsessive-compulsive,
but let's do this right now.
No way!
Lloyd.
What?
Get away from me!
What did I do?
Don't even follow me!
Don't do this.
Leave me alone!
Don't make me sound
like a counselor, Lloyd.
I've got statistics I can show you.
I have graphs I can show you.
I got all this stuff I can show you.
It all says the same thing.
You have to decide
on a career.
[Sighs]
My dad's a lieutenant-colonel
in the army.
He wants me to join.
He wants to pull some strings.
I mean, there's no possible way.
Let me just make
an appointment for you
at Seattle Junior College.
You the key master?
Yep.
I'm not gonna go
to Seattle Junior College.
I've gotta be honest with you.
I'm not looking for that.
I'm looking for something bigger.
I'm looking for
a dare-to-be-great situation.
Lloyd, everybody
in that party put something
on their record except you.
How many of 'em really know
what they want though?
A lot of them think they
have to know, right?
But inside they don't really know.
So, I don't know.
But I know
that I don't know.
[Pats Shoulder]
Hang tough, Lloyd.
[Keys Clink]
I know we were "all too competitive" this year,
but I just want to say...
that if it wasn't
for "Diane Court"- whoa-
I probably wouldn't
have gotten into Cornell,
because you made me study
twice as hard.
- So thanks.
- You did the same for me.
I did?
[Chattering, Laughing]
Did you really come here
with Lloyd Dobler?
How did that "happen"?
He made me laugh.
Yes. He's okay, Dad.
I- You're welcome.
I always call you.
You know that.
[Girl] Call you?
All right, um—
Stop being so grateful.
All right. I'll-I'll be home
before dawn, okay?
Bye.
Dawn?
Oh, would you guys
sign my annual?
Sure.
- Would you sign mine?
- Yeah.
Did you really have
to call your dad?
God, how nightmarish.
- I promised.
- Is he gonna wait up?
Tell him nothing.
Nothing.
I make sure I enter
the house crying.
He leaves me alone.
I loved in your speech
when you said
you were scared.
Lloyd Dobler.
All right.
♪♪ [Ska On Stereo]
[Laughing]
♪ He ♪
♪ Likes girls ♪
[Girl Giggles]
Whatever you say, Brian.
♪ With names ♪
♪ Like Ashleigh ♪
♪ And Tammerlane ♪♪
Hey, what's up, man?
How's it goin'?
I'll be in
the kitchen, Joe.
♪ That'll never be me
That'll never be me ♪
♪ That'll never be
Never be me, no ♪
♪ That'll never be me
That'll never be me ♪
♪ That'll never be
Never be me, no ♪
Joe, Joe.
♪♪ [Continues, Indistinct]
She's written 65 songs.
Sixty-five.
They're all about you.
They're all about pain.
So what's up?
So stop freaking with
her head, man. Stop playing
with her mind, you know?
She's a human being.
She's a person.
She's very talented, you know?
Dude, why do you think
I keep her tapes, man?
Gonna be valuable some day.
♪ No, never♪
♪ No, never ever, ever
Don't you ever think it ♪♪
Oh, my God!
[Groans]
♪♪ [Rock On Stereo]
Joe was my first love.
He was my first sex.
And the whole time,
he was going out with Mimi.
He'll never break up with her.
But if I see him,
it's, "Hi, Joe. How are you?"
And that is it. I'll be okay.
Don't worry.
He's at the other end of the house.
It's too bad more guys
can't be like Lloyd.
- He checks up on me. Look.
- Oh.
I've got more songs to do.
♪Joe lies ♪
♪ When he cries ♪
[Laughs]
♪ When he cries ♪♪
So we can finally talk.
Yeah.
Well- What?
[Bullhorn Chirping]
Lakewood, Lakewood
have no fear!
How about another year?
[All Shouting]
He does this every year?
The worst job
since key master.
Hi, Joe.
How are you?
I love you.
I love you too.
You invade my soul.
I wanna
get back together.
Mimi's gonna go to college,
and I'm gonna be alone.
But I'm gonna break up with her
before she leaves.
Have sex with me.
Ahh!
Good-bye, Joe.
[Pats Shoulder]
[Loudly]
You know, every year I throw this party.
Every year nobody helps me clean up.
Why am I yelling?
I don't know.
We're outta here, man.
- All right, Lloyd. Thanks.
- Maybe we'll come by tomorrow,
help you clean up.
Diane, everybody loved
that you showed up.
[Chuckles]
You're a great rooster.
Well-
Sign this?
Okay.
[Lloyd] Hey, Cor.
So I'm single now.
Everything's changed. I hate it.
[Lloyd Grunts]
Give me my Firebird keys!
You must chill!
I have hidden your keys.
Chill!
I love you, man.
All right.
I love you too.
Go to sleep.
We're full-on buds.
Yeah, right!
[Grunts]
Later.
Hey.
You're such
a great person, Lloyd.
I'm a good person,
but you are a great person.
We're outta there, man.
Yes.
See you tomorrow.
See ya.
[Diane]
Bye.
Bye, Diane.
Bye-bye.
[Vahlere]
Hey, drive safe.
[Sighs]
Thank you.
I hereby surrender
my duties as key master.
Gimme a beer.
Certainly.
I'm happy to say
that this sack
is officially empty.
Uh-oh.
The back bathroom.
Let's go.
Oh, look at
this gentleman here.
[Mike] I gotta get home.
Gotta get home.
[Burps]
Oop. Excuse me.
[All Chuckling]
I'm sorry.
How you doin',
brother?
[Mike Clears Throat]
You know, I don't even know
where we are.
[Deejay On Radio]
I'm about to play you three hours
of commercial-free rock and roll—
[Continues, Indistinct]
I love this album.
It's a good one.
♪♪ [Rock]
[Groans]
You like it?
[Lloyd]
Do you recognize anything yet?
Anything?
♪♪ [Rock]
[Deejay]
Lord, have mercy.
Three hours of
commercial-free rock and roll.
Good morning.
Hey, that's it!
That's my house!
I live there.
[Tires Screech]
Well, uh,
have a good sleep.
Bye.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, you guys are the best.
Give me a call, or, uh-
[Woman On Radio]
♪ Looking at you tonight ♪
[Chuckles]
♪♪ [Continues, Indistinct]
Look at this one.
Uh, did you-
So what did they write
in your book? What did
they write to Diane Court?
All right.
Listen to some of the things
they wrote me.
"Glad I finally met you."
"You always seemed nice."
"Wish I could've
known you more."
Mine says stuff like, uh,
"Lloyd, see you around maybe."
Nobody knew me
before tonight.
They knew of you.
Now they know you.
Yeah, but I feel like I fit in
for the first time, you know?
Like I held them
far away from me,
so they did
the same to me.
That's cool then.
Yeah.
I'm so glad we did this.
We can walk
from here.
Okay.
So it’s just you
and your dad, right?
Yeah.
That's a whole story
you don't want to hear.
Sure I do.
Hmm.
Well, my parents split up
when I was 13, and-
God, I actually had to-
I went to court,
and I had to choose
between the two of them.
So I chose my dad.
Just felt safer that way,
you know?
Watch out for that glass.
Thanks.
But either way,
it's still—
Yeah, twisted.
You know what?
What?
You're a great date.
I've never really
gone out with someone
as basic as you.
Basic. Huh!
So what's your job
this summer?
Job? Being a great date.
No, I'm serious.
So am I.
I want to see you again-
as much as I can
before you leave. Said it!
I only have something
like 16 weeks.
Sixteen weeks
is a long time.
Then call me tomorrow.
Today is tomorrow.
Then call me later.
Okay.
[Diane Giggles]
Thanks.
I'll-I'll call you later.
[Door Creaks, Closes]
Good morning, honey.
Dad, I'm so glad I went.
Good night.
Uh, wait, wait,
wait a minute.
How was Lloyd?
[Exhales]
Lloyd was such a gentleman.
He was funny
and nervous and strange.
And I met people
I would have never met before.
And then I blew it.
I called him "basic."
[Chuckles]
Can you believe
I did that?
Well-
I don't think he's reeling
in embarrassment.
[Giggles]
Good night.
Yes!
- [Corey]
Lloyd is doomed.
- Meaning?
Meaning that she made
the second date
a family audition,
which is the kiss of death
for Lloyd.
Why?
It's too much pressure.
It's not his crowd.
- What's wrong with this girl?
- I told him to be himself.
But he's got that
nervous talking thing.
I told him not to speak.
I know this is a strange thing to say,
but maybe Diane Court
really likes Lloyd.
If you were Diane Court,
would you honestly
fall for Lloyd?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
[Laughs]
[Clattering]
- You think I should
wear this dress?
- Yeah.
Or—
Or I could always wear this one.
That's nice.
[Sniffing]
Oh, um, I forgot to tell you
who'll be at the dinner tonight.
Uh, my dad's accountant,
um, and two women that work
in his nursing home.
I know you don't know them,
but it'll be fun.
Boy, this is
a mother dictionary!
I know.
I've had it forever.
I used to have this thing
with marking the words
I looked up.
Or I have this one.
That's a nice one.
Yeah?
Yeah, you should
wear that.
Mm-hmm. Think so?
Mm-hmm.
[Doorbell Rings]
Get— Better get
downstairs, huh?
Yeah. I gotta change.
♪♪ [Dave Brubeck Quartet: "Take Five"]
[Man]
It's a great meal, you two.
[Woman]
You just look beautiful, Diane.
Oh, thank you.
Same eyes, same nose,
same mouth. See what
a few millimeters can do?
[Man]
So, what airline do they
send you over to England on?
- A charter.
- She's not the world's greatest flier.
Let me tell ya.
When she was
eight years old, she-
Dad.
- Now, why can't I tell the story?
- [Woman] What story?
- If you’re gonna tell it, let me tell it.
- Well, let me start.
I'm flying down to Los Angeles
on business,
and I decide to take her
on her first airplane.
I knew how planes flew,
but I was still a little nervous.
- Crash paranoia.
- Oh.
I had a checklist in mind.
I thought if babies were on the plane,
the plane couldn't crash.
But all the babies were crying,
and I thought they knew
something I didn't.
So anyway,
they close the doors
and she starts to scream.
I never in my life
heard anybody scream
like that.
Then you got up, and you told
them to turn the plane around.
Which they did.
Let me finish.
Okay, I give up.
So anyway, these two
federal marshals meet the plane,
and they take our address,
and they ask us never to fly
the friendly skies again.
[Chuckles]
You never flew?
[Sighs]
No. But there's more.
Oh, yeah! There was, um—
Somebody on the plane
worked in a recording studio.
And we get this
telephone call,
and this guy's making
a sound-effects record,
and he'd gotten our address,
and he wanted to
know if he could come over
and record her scream.
Which they did.
And every once in a while
on a commercial...
you can hear me scream.
[Chuckling]
You two are amazing.
You know?
They way— They way-
The way you talk.
I'm just like—
I'm not even like that
with anybody.
It's a stellar jukebox, sir.
Thanks, Lloyd.
How do you obtain
one of those?
Uh, what did we pay
for the Wurlitzer, Al?
Well, that guy didn't
want to part with it.
A little matter of, uh, $9,000?
- So, Lloyd, you graduated
Lakewood, right?
- Yes, sir.
What are you gonna do now?
Yeah, Lloyd.
What are your plans for the future?
Spend as much time
as possible with Diane
before, uh, she leaves.
Seriously, Lloyd.
I'm totally
and completely serious.
No, really.
You mean, like, career?
Um-
I don't know. If, uh-
[Clears Throat]
I've thought about this
quite a bit, sir.
I would have to say,
considering what's waiting
out there for me,
I don't want to sell anything,
buy anything or process anything
as a career.
I don't want to sell anything
bought or processed,
or buy anything sold or processed,
or... process anything
sold, bought...
or processed,
or repair anything
sold, bought or processed.
You know, as a career,
I don't want to do that.
So, uh, my father's in the army.
He wants me to join,
but I can't work for that corporation.
Um, so what I've been
doing lately is kickboxing.
Which is a, uh, new sport,
but I think it's...
got a good future.
As far as career longevity,
I don't really know, because,
you know, you can't really tell.
If you’re eight-and-six
as a fighter, it's no good.
You have to be great.
But I can't tell if
I'm great until I've had
a couple of pro fights.
But I haven't
been knocked down yet.
I don't know. I can't figure
it all out tonight, so I'm just
gonna hang with your daughter.
Hello.
Mr. James Court?
Yeah. Can I help you?
I'm Mr. Sims,
and this is Mr. Talbot.
We're special agents
of the Internal Revenue Service.
And we'd like to inform you
that you are under
criminal investigation...
for the tax years
1982 through 1986.
Jesus. What, I live
in a palace, right?
I have guests here.
Understanding
the following rights—
Speak with my lawyer.
So you refuse
to answer my questions?
Just come down to my place
of business, for God's sake.
I have people here.
Mr. Court, be aware that
we will be contacting a number
of your business associates—
This evening is over.
and your former wife.
Mom, please.
Diane, I do have a history
with this man,
and it's not the greatest.
I see you so seldom,
I'd really rather hear about you.
This is me
telling you about me.
You know, I don't even know
if you’ve got a young man in your life.
I just wonder what could be more important
than what's going on with Dad.
[Sighs]
If we could just talk about boys,
everything would be so much easier.
You know, your room
is always ready for you.
You can come home if you want.
All right.
What do you want me to do?
If they ask you questions—
and they probably will ask you questions-
would you please say
something nice about him, Mom?
Help him?
All right.
You will?
Okay.
Oh, here's Ray.
Just talk to him,
'cause when you don't
your mouth turns down.
Hi, honey.
Hello, pretty ladies.
Mmm!
Mm-wah!
Hi, Diane.
Hi, Ray.
So what are you
doing after work?
[Diane] I usually have
a break after the dinner service
if you want to stop by.
Want to do something later?
I know you think my job
is strange. You don't like
old people, do you?
Me? Sure I do.
Come on.
Well, except for one thing.
I used to work
at a smorgasbord,
and, you know, the old people
would flock there,
and they loved to eat.
They'd just jam their mouths,
you know? They just would
eat with their mouths open.
To be honest,
it’s just too much for me.
I mean, you—
you get to be thinking
about how short life is...
and how maybe-
maybe everything
has no meaning.
Because you wake up,
and then you're
frying burgers,
and then you're, like,
60 and 70, and then,
you know, you check out.
And what are you doing?
I just don't need to think
about those kinds of things.
So that— that's the reason
I was, um-
But I'm not sure I'm right
about any of that.
I think that's ageism.
That's being prejudiced against
people because they're old.
Maybe their mouths
don't work as well as yours.
Really?
Um— I- Well-
You're really turning me around here.
I was just looking at it the wrong way, I think.
Should I still come by?
Stop by later.
Okay.
All right, I will.
Okay, bye.
I'll-I'll see you later.
Bye.
You have to meet Bess.
Okay.
She's amazing.
She's 93, she's a writer,
and I told her about you.
Wait a minute.
You told her about me?
Yes.
What'd you say?
Um—
Just meet her.
Hi.
This is Bess.
Lloyd, Bess.
Hello.
You're too tall.
[Laughs]
- She likes you.
- [Laughs]
- Okay, how you doing? Hello.
- [Person Clapping]
Uh, I'm Lloyd.
[Woman Chattering]
[Man Coughs]
We're gonna watch this movie Cocoon.
I've never actually seen it.
I hear it's very good.
I hear it makes you very happy.
I figure that's a good film to see-
one that makes you happy.
It's about
a group of older people
who go to outer space.
Hope I didn't
give anything away there.
The movie hasn't started yet.
We're gonna have a good time.
Thank you.
[Man]
Are you going to stay and watch?
[Diane] Sure, we'll both stay.
[Woman]
Why can't I eat popcorn anymore?
I'll get you something.
Okay. So, here we go
with Cocoon.
So they're cool.
That was good.
Good, good, good.
[Exhales]
[Chuckles]
I feel so bad being with you.
I feel selfish.
I feel like I should be
spending more time with my dad.
I mean, it's not fair to you,
when half the time I'm with you
I'm thinking of other things.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Everybody does that.
I just don't want it
to get too heavy.
I feel really overloaded.
I have this theory of convergence that
good things always happen with bad things.
I mean, like, I know you have to deal with them
at the same, you know, time.
But I just- I don't know why
they have to happen at the same time.
I mean, I don't know why. I just wish
I could work out some sort of schedule.
- Am I just babbling?
Do you know what I mean?
- No.
[Laughs]
I just can't have
any social life right now.
Don't worry about it.
We’re just having coffee. We'll be antisocial.
- Be friends?
- Yeah, with potential.
Ah, friends with potential.
[Lloyd]
Yeah, keep going in first.
Keep going around. Get the feel of it.
Feel the clutch.
If you put it in a little?
Yeah?
You know how it'll
come out, and it feels,
you know—
Little more, little more.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
That's all right.
Go around just in first.
Just feel it.
Right.
It's kind of all right.
Yeah.
But now when I-
When you feel confident-
Yeah?
If you’ll just maybe
ease it into second.
[Gears Grinding]
Well, all right.
Put it— Put it—
[Laughs, Mutters]
All right, listen.
Am I wrecking my car
with this?
This is very important.
Yeah, you are a little bit.
But listen. It's important.
When you feel it start to give,
put the clutch in.
Oh!
When you feel-
I was putting the gas on
when I felt—
Yeah, 'cause then—
A little more gas, more gas. Ease it out.
All right.
No— Minor setback.
[Laughs]
Now that you're
feeling confident, right?
Yeah?
You feel better about it.
Now go into second.
A little more gas.
[Engine Revving]
Yeah! You get this—
You get this, no problem.
[Fingers Snap]
Hey.
Now maybe you'll downshift...
to first.
[Engine Revs]
[Tires Screech Briefly]
Oh.
[Chuckles]
Does it sound normal?
Well, no,
it's not normal,
but as you get better,
you hear less of it.
[Engine Stops]
[Laughs]
Brake, brake. Get the brake.
[Brake Sets]
[Laughs]
Let's switch.
You wanna switch?
Yeah.
I'll drive? All right.
- [Diane Laughing]
- [Horn Honks]
[Lloyd Laughs]
I'm sorry.
[Diane]
[Murmurs]
- Let's get out of here.
You want to?
- [Diane] Yeah.
Okay.
[Tires Squealing]
- [Diane Kisses, Sighs]
- [Man On Stereo, Low]
♪ I get so lost sometimes ♪
♪ Days pass ♪
[Continues]
Are you comfortable?
Yes.
♪ When I want
to run away ♪
♪ I drive off♪
♪ In my car♪
♪ But whichever way I go ♪
♪ I come back
to the place you are ♪
[Shivering Quietly]
Are you shaking?
♪ All my instincts ♪
No.
♪ They return ♪
You're shaking.
♪♪ [Continues]
I don't think so.
You're cold.
♪ Without a noise ♪
I don't think I am.
Then why are you shaking?
♪ Without my pride ♪
I don't know.
I think I'm happy.
♪ I reach out from the inside ♪
[Shivering]
Here's some blanket.
♪ In your eyes
The light, the heat ♪
Listen to this song.
It's a really good song.
♪ In your eyes ♪
♪ I am complete ♪
♪ I see the doorway ♪
♪ In your eyes ♪
♪ To a thousand churches ♪♪
[Sighs Quietly]
[Footsteps On Stairs]
Good morning.
Dad, I'm sorry.
You should be.
I was irresponsible.
I should've called.
You bet you should've called!
You still live at home.
Don't make me call the police
at 3:30 in the morning.
Don't make me call hospitals!
Dad, I'm so sorry.
I know this is a bad time.
You've always called before, always.
Now I'm not asking what you did.
I just wanna know
if you’re all right.
I'm fine.
You wanna make
things easier on me?
Then tell me where you were.
Because this is-
this is bullshit!
You can say anything to me.
I hope you still know that.
I know that.
I spent the night with him.
- Lloyd?
- Dad, yes.
And... I'm scared to death
of what you must think
of me right now.
[Quietly] Sit down.
Dad, do you know
what he did the first night
I went out with him?
We were walking across
by the 7-Eleven,
and... he pointed out some glass
for me to walk around.
And I always think
of that when people say,
"What are you doing with Lloyd Dobler?"
And— And I never
get nervous around him.
So we started spending
all this time together... as friends.
But—
[Sighs]
I could feel him getting anxious.
And then... I knew that
there would be a confrontation
over getting physical.
[Clears Throat]
He started to get that look
at the end of the night.
- Do you know that look?
- [Mouths Word]
And then, you know
it's gonna be an issue.
So I went through
all the different feelings...
and all the different arguments
you're supposed to go through.
- Did he ever get rough with you?
- Dad, no.
But I didn't want any problems,
so I decided not to sleep with him.
But then I attacked him anyway.
[Chuckles]
[Sighs]
It always feels good
to tell you the truth.
Because if I can't share it with you,
it's almost like it didn't happen.
- [Corey]
Did you sleep with her?
- ♪♪ [Strumming Rock, Quietly]
I admit nothing.
Lloyd?
- It's us.
- ♪♪ [Continues Strumming]
Look at his face.
He did the deed.
You're an inspiration, Lloyd.
You should go on The 700 Club
or something.
All right, all right, all right.
Calm down, all right? Calm down.
Nothing's different.
Lloyd, listen to me.
Everything has changed.
You've had sex.
♪♪ [Continues, Quietly]
No matter what you might think,
nothing will ever be the same
between you two.
You might be 60.
You might be walking
down the street,
and you'll talk to her
about something, whatever,
but what you'll really
be thinking is,
"We had sex."
[Chuckles]
What's the point?
You've got to do something special.
- You've got to make a statement.
- Wait a minute. I—
You've got
to show her respect.
- You've got to show her
that you're not like Joe.
- Wait a minute.
And above all,
just because this happened,
gives you no right whatsoever-
- I always sit here listening,
and you never let me talk.
- What? I'm sorry. Talk.
[Sighs]
I forgot what I was gonna say.
♪♪ [Resumes, Stops]
Okay.
Okay, I remember.
- Let him do what he wants.
- All right.
Yes!
Lloyd, send her flowers
or write her a letter
or something.
- I already did.
- What's it say?
-Just read it.
- I can read it?
[Quietly]
Oh, man.
[Sighs]
"Dear Diane,
"I'll always
be there for you.
All the love
in my heart, Lloyd."
♪♪ [Resumes, Slowly]
I've never gotten
a letter like this.
Have you?
I dream about it.
So what do you think?
Is it— Is it—
You think it'll—
Get ready for greatness,
Lloyd.
♪♪ [Resumes:
"Summertime Blues"]
The, uh, Cynthia Bramson estate
was worth how much?
Because her family-
What family?
We never heard from them.
I sold a house for her
and made her money.
Mm-hmm.
Your income, Mr. Court,
hasn't changed substantially-
- Thank you.
- in 17 years.
That's right.
Why would you stay so long
with an operation—
Please, some coffee, Mr. Court.
that is so clearly not
a growth enterprise?
Taking care of people
isn't a growth enterprise, Mr. Sims.
I hope you write that down.
I'd like your bosses to read it.
♪♪ [Pop On Stereo]
♪♪ [Humming]
[Door Closes]
Diane.
Your ticket to England
came today.
Dad, maybe I shouldn't go,
with all that's happening to you.
You're going.
But listen. If I had a friend
in the same position,
I would tell her
to delay a year.
You're going.
It doesn't feel right to me.
I- I don't even have
the right luggage yet.
Bon voyage.
- You're not listening to me.
- Diane, all right.
Now let's stop this right now.
Let's not put our energy
into something ridiculous.
This isn't even
smart thinking.
Dad, why are you acting this way?
Is this because of the other morning?
Do you love him?
I like him a lot.
Well, listen to me.
Now, I know you like him.
I know he's nothin' like
these frat kids you can't stand.
But, honey,
after the excitement wears off,
then what, huh?
I mean,
what are you gonna talk about?
What do you have in common?
You're gonna be part
of an international
think tank,
and he's gonna be...
kicking punching bags.
I just think you should
break up with him.
Unbelievable.
This is nightmarish.
Diane, you owe it
to yourself...
to get on that plane
with no attachments,
no strings.
Because after
you get over there,
things are gonna change.
People change.
Dad, you and I
have talked about this.
Lloyd and I have talked
about this. Believe me,
this is well-covered territory.
Diane, I'm not asking you
to sever all relations
with the boy. I—
Uh, give him a present. Here.
Let him know you still care.
Give him this pen.
A pen.
Dad, in a million years,
I would never give him
a pen.
What's wrong with having
some fun? I like him.
"I like him"?
I'm talking about being honest
with people, being decent—
Dad, I love him.
[Stirring Stops]
Great.
No, that's great. I-
It's great
to hear you say that,
because-
I don't know.
What, am I being selfish?
I-
Why am I so fixated?
[Sighs]
I guess it's because
I got a lot of troubles with-
I-
Is that it? Am I—
Am I being selfish?
I just want you to have everything.
Is that wrong?
No, uh-
I owe you an apology.
[Pot Lid Rattles]
Just got a handful of weeks left
with you, and we should—
[Stammers]
I don't know. I don't know
what I'm trying to say.
They think I'm guilty.
Some computer
spits out your name,
and another honest man-
[Quietly]
What's the goddamn point?
Live your life.
I love you.
Oh, Dad, I'm so sorry.
[Children Shout Greeting]
All right. Now power left!
Power right!
[Phone Rings]
All right, who's world champion?
Who's your hero?
[Children Shouting]
Don "The Dragon" Wilson!
[Indistinct Shout]
[Man]
Lloyd, telephone!
Keep kickin'. Kick the-
[Indistinct]
[Chattering]
Hello?
Hi.
How are you doin'?
[Chattering]
Yeah, they actually
pay me for this.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll pick you up
in an hour.
See you later.
You should check
your mail tomorrow.
I sent you, uh, a letter,
a blue letter.
Your letter came yesterday.
It did?
Uh-huh.
It was wonderful.
I wish—
Why didn't you tell me?
It was wonderful.
I never sent a letter
like that, you know?
I mean, I sent it. Well-
I don't know. I felt like
I wanted to tell you somethin'
I didn't put in the letter.
I didn't say it, but I think
I wanna say it now. But I'm
not sure if I should say it,
'cause people always say it
when they don't mean it,
but I think I mean it.
So, um, I just wanted
to tell you that-
No. We don't have to say it.
How do you know
what I'm gonna say?
I don't know.
I was gonna tell you
I love you.
But if you think you—
I said it.
I know.
[Diane Sighs]
Lloyd, let's not start
putting things on this level.
What? This is a good level.
Isn't it?
How can I look at you
and say this?
Say what?
I think that we should
spend some time apart.
What's wrong?
Well,
I need to study, and I—
You need to study?
Yeah.
Okay. How much time do you need?
I mean, you know?
I mean, you're gonna be leaving
in a little while, so I'm just
asking questions.
We'll see.
[Vehicle Passes, Honks Horn]
Okay.
It's good knowing this.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
[Engine Slows, Stops]
[Key Turns]
Wait a minute.
What did we just decide?
[Sighs]
We decided-
Because I'm worried.
Did you just break up with me?
No. No—
It sounded like you did.
No.
We decided that we're friends.
I mean, I know
it's a terrible word—
Well, if we’re friends,
why can't we see each other?
I think that we should
stop going out on dates.
Oh.
I feel like a dick.
You must think
I'm a dick.
No, I don't.
I don't.
Yeah, you do.
Lloyd, we shared
the most intimate thing
two people can share.
You shared it
with a dick.
No, I didn't.
Is this because
of your dad?
No.
You talk to Corey?
Why? Did you tell Corey
what happened?
She figured it out. I'm sorry
if that upsets you, but—
No, that's fine.
She'll tell everybody,
but that's fine.
Did you tell
anybody?
Just my dad.
Y-You told your dad?
You have Corey and D.C.
I have my dad.
What? I'm sorry I said that.
Forget I said it. I said
what I thought I meant, but-
Lloyd-
forget it.
I love you, okay?
What is that? What are you doing
with your hands?
Don't— Don't be—
Talk to me. One party and you're
talking like that girl Sheila.
Don't be mean.
This is hard for me too.
Then don't do it.
[Quietly]
Oh, shit.
[Zipper Opening]
[Rustling]
Would you just take this pen,
please, and write me?
[Sniffles]
I don't believe this.
You just broke up with me.
[Engine Starts]
[Sighs]
[Crying]
Hello, Constance?
It's me, Lloyd.
Nothing,
I'm just driving around.
She broke up with me.
What do I do?
Think she'll come back?
How can I get her back? Can't-
Can't get her to talk to me.
It's all so fucked up.
I feel like crying.
She gave me a pen.
I gave her my heart,
and she gave me a pen.
[Sighs]
Lloyd, honey,
just come home, okay?
I'll be home soon.
[Man On TV]
My friends still don't know what
they're gonna do after graduation.
But I've already locked in
guaranteed skill training...
in the army.
Qualify now,
and you can reserve
for even...
the army's most sought-after
technical training-
up to 12 months in advance.
[Switch Clicks]
It's me, cruisin' around.
It's pretty late. I know
I haven't called you lately,
'cause I didn't want
to be reminded
of the Diane nightmare.
By the way,
I hardly remember-
I've wiped her from my mind.
I don't remember the time
and place when I knew her.
Yeah, this is it-
the site of our controversial
first date. I met her in a mall.
Should have known
our relationship
was doomed.
To our left we have the street
where she broke up with me.
There's the path we took.
Corey, I guess in a way
I blamed you. I held it against you,
lettin' me send that letter.
But I don't know. I thought
it was the right thing too.
I think I know too many girls.
You know, I should hang out
with more guys. I should be
like one of those guys...
who hangs out at the am/pm
or the Gas 'N Sip on a Saturday.
But I don't know.
Guys like that
really know the answers?
- Lloyd, man,
no babe is worth it, dude.
- [Others Affirming]
Listen, hang with us, man.
We'll teach you bibles full of truth.
Right.
Lloyd, man, you can't even trust 'em, man,
because you know what it's about?
They spend your money,
and they tell their friends everything, man.
It's about economics.
They tell 'em everything.
That's valid, man.
Man, all you gotta do is find a girl
who looks just like her,
nail her
and then dump her, man.
Dump her, man!
Get her off your mind.
Your only mistake is that
you didn't dump her first.
Diane Court is a show pony.
You need a stallion, my friend.
Walk with us
and you walk tall.
Walk tall, my man.
Bitches, man.
[Watch Beeps]
- Hey, dude, I better bail.
- [Others Saying Farewells]
[Sniffs]
I got a question.
If you guys know so much
about women,
how come you're here
at, like, a Gas 'N Sip
on a Saturday night...
completely alone,
drinkin' beers
and no women anywhere?
Well, it's-
[Clears Throat]
By choice, man.
That's right.
- It's a conscious choice.
- It's a choice, man.
We're choosin'
to be here.
We all wanna be here.
I'm choosin' it.
Dude, where'd
she dump you, man?
- In a car.
- Your car?
Ah, man!
Dissed in the Malibu?
Oh, heinous!
- Hey, that's your castle, man.
- Ah, you never had a chance
with a girl like that.
[Boy In Hat]
Hey, man,
I was in love once, man.
I got hurt really bad.
I never want to go
through that again.
Man, you're bringin' me down!
Shut up, man.
We're goin' to a kegger, Lloyd.
We're goin' to a kegger,
and we'd like you to come, man.
We're gonna find you a girl.
We're gonna find you a babe, man.
We're gonna find you
one hot-lit babe instantly!
Promise.
Nope, nope.
That's right, man.
One hot-lit babe
instantly!
Look, I'm-
I'm not going to meet somebody
like Diane Court at a kegger.
This girl was different, man.
When we'd go out, we wouldn't
even have to go out, you know?
We'd just hang out.
The girl made me
trust myself, man.
I was walkin' around,
I was feelin' satisfied.
Can you imagine that?
Then she cuts me loose.
I don't know why.
She won't tell me why.
Who knows the real reason?
[Sniffles]
Maybe it's 'cause of her father.
I don't know.
- She won't talk to me.
She won't look at me.
- [Bottle Shatters]
Come on! You're freakin' out!
Christ, Lloyd.
What is up with you?
You're wiggin', man.
♪ L-Lloyd's- ♪
Chill, man. Come on.
♪ He's wiggin', man ♪
♪ He's wiggin' ♪
♪ [Scats] He's wiggin', ho ♪
Dude, I don't even feel
that way about my car, man.
♪ He's wiggin' every day ♪
♪ But lookin' every night ♪
♪♪ [Continues]
Dude, name a babe, all right?
Any babe in Seattle.
I'll set you up with her.
♪ He's not sure
what to do ♪
Diane Court!
Dude, I can't do it, buddy.
♪♪ [Beat-boxing]
♪ Lloyd, Lloyd
all null and void ♪
♪ Listen to the truth
he's tryin' to avoid ♪
Hey.
♪ Lloyd thinks she's all special
but she’s just another ho ♪♪
[Switch Clicks]
That was a mistake.
The rain on my car
is a baptism.
I'm the new me.
Ice man. Power Lloyd.
My assault on the world
begins now.
I believe in myself,
answer to no one.
You probably got it
all figured out, Corey.
If you start out depressed,
everything's kind of
a pleasant surprise.
Look. Why don't you
just call Diane again?
I draw the line
at seven unreturned phone calls.
[Corey] Lloyd,
you have to understand,
her family is being ripped apart-
like you and she
were ripped apart.
Like Joe and I
- Visit her at the home.
- I'm not goin' back there.
I don't even know
who you're talkin' about.
Why do you have to be like this?
Because I'm a guy.
I have pride.
You're not a guy.
- I am.
- No. No, the world is full of guys.
Be a man. Don't be a guy.
If she wants me,
she can come to me.
[Answering Machine Beeps]
[Lloyd On Speaker]
Hi. Lloyd.
This is my eighth
and final call. Um-
Well, go ahead,
pick it up if you want.
I just wanted to say
that I thought about everything,
and I decided something.
I gonna give you another chance.
Maybe no one's listening,
or maybe your father is listening.
Hey, Mr. Court. If you’re
listening to this, hello.
How are you?
- If I pick it up, we'll only get back together.
- Then don't.
- You know what's best.
- Anyway, maybe I didn't know you.
Maybe you're a mirage.
Maybe the world is a blur
of food and sex and spectacle,
and everyone's hurtling towards
an acropolis, in which case
it's not your fault, you know?
Maybe it's a good side to this.
I've been thinking about things.
You're probably
standing there monitoring.
So just, uh, one other thing.
The letter that I wrote you—
could you please rip it up?
[Sighs]
Nuke it. Flame it.
Destroy it. It hurts me
to know it's out there.
Will you do that for me?
[Sniffles]
All right. Later.
Hello?
[Line Clicks, Dial Tone]
Hi.
Is it a gift for your wife?
We could put a set together.
No, I'm not married.
It's for my daughter.
Oh, going to school.
Yeah, she won
a fellowship.
Good for her.
Uh-huh.
[Chuckles]
I'll take the whole set.
Excellent.
[Chuckles]
[Sighs, Chuckles]
I gotta tell you. You-
You got the best smile
I've seen all week.
Thanks. I like yours too.
[Chuckles]
Listen, I don't know
your name, but, uh-
[Machine Beeps]
what are you doin'
for lunch?
Um, I'm sorry,
but they turned down your card.
Oh. Well, here, then let me
give you another card.
Thank you.
[Chuckling]
Thanks.
[Machine Beeps]
[Sighs]
I- I'm afraid I can't accept
this one either.
There's a... "decline" code
on your account.
I'm supposed
to confiscate your card,
but why don't you just-
[Whispers]
go ahead and take it?
Oh, keep it.
You sure?
Yeah, I don't want it. Um-
Uh, thank you very much.
You've been very kind.
[Knocking]
[Diane]
Dad, are you okay in there?
I'm just finishing up in here.
[Crickets Chirping
In Distance]
[Sighs]
♪♪ [Man On Stereo,
In Distance, Faint]
[Sighs]
[In Distance, Louder]
♪ When I want to run away ♪
♪ I drive off♪
♪ In my car♪
♪ But whichever way I go ♪
♪ I come back to the place you are ♪
♪ All my instincts ♪
♪ They return ♪
♪ And the grand facade ♪
♪ So soon will burn ♪
♪ Without a noise ♪
♪ Without my pride ♪
♪ I reach out from the inside ♪
♪♪ [Vocalizing]
♪ In your eyes ♪
♪ The light, the heat ♪
♪ I am complete ♪
♪ In your eyes ♪
♪ I see the doorway ♪
♪ To a thousand churches ♪
♪ In your eyes ♪
♪ The resolution ♪
♪ Of all the fruitless searches ♪♪
[Chattering]
Regarding
James Court.
Room 14.
Thanks.
I'm supposed to be leaving
on a fellowship...
that I worked for
my entire life,
and I don't even care.
I met this boy over the summer,
and I- I can't see him
because of this, and I can't-
I can't talk to him.
I can't talk to my father
about this.
And I wore these clothes.
I thought- I thought that...
if I looked right,
and if I acted right,
then someone would talk to me.
But I look awful,
and I feel awful. Could you-
Could you please talk to me?
Be a little decent.
All right.
We believe that your father
operates from a large pool of cash...
that comes from phony billing,
phony patients.
We've been investigating him
for five years.
We believe, when they die,
he takes their money.
Pardon me?
Look, why don't you
check it out for yourself.
See if your father
fits the profile.
- What's the profile?
- Well, take a look around the house.
Is everything nice
but not too nice?
Are there a lot of, uh, rugs,
pieces of art, stereo equipment,
uh, furniture-
a lot of things
bought with cash?
Does he give a lot of gifts?
Do the major items in your house
hover around the $9,000 range?
You're trying to get me
to say something.
That's why you’re telling me this.
Don't let your father's business
infect your life.
How can you—
How can you say that?
- Because he's guilty.
- No. He's not.
We have the records.
We have the proof.
I'm sorry to be the one
to have to tell you this,
but it's going to get worse.
Now if I were you,
I would take that fellowship.
Dad?
Anybody home?
They made me doubt you.
[Shoving Bills Together]
[Tires Squeal]
[Hinges Creak]
What happened to you?
Dad, did you do it?
Did you take that money?
Sweetheart, no.
Don't be ridiculous.
Swear to God.
I need to know the truth.
Honey!
Swear to God.
I swear to God.
I found the money.
Honey, it's not what you think.
What am I supposed
to think?
Well, honey, about what?
You stole from them! You lied to me!
How do you think that's supposed
to make me feel?
Oh, think you know
what this money is?
Yes, I-
No, you don't know what it is!
It's not for me.
This money's for you,
for when you come back
from England with honors,
to set you up
so you never have to depend
on anybody again.
Diane, I take better care
of those people
than their families do.
I care for them. I give them flowers.
I feed them. I wipe their mouths.
- No, but you stole from them!
- I make their lives better!
You let me defend you.
And you knew you were guilty,
and you let me become a part of it!
God, Dad, how could—
All right. All right, go ahead.
When I'm old, give me someone like me,
but go ahead.
I trusted you.
I stood up in court five years ago,
and I picked you.
Why are you being
so hateful to me?
- Is this because of Lloyd?
- No.
I told you everything,
and you lied to me.
I would have done
anything for you.
That's right. Work it out.
No. I will.
I don't want to leave
something out, 'cause I know
I can say anything to you.
You're a liar and a thief.
Take it easy
how bad you make me.
I'm the only dad you've got.
[Groans]
[Quietly]
I'm so ashamed. Dad.
No, don't say that.
It's not good for you. Don't-
You're right.
No, talk- Diane?
Wait. Diane?
Wait a minute!
Now talk—
[Typing]
Hey, Lloyd,
someone's here to see you.
[Grunts]
Lloyd?
[Quietly]
God.
[Sighs]
Lloyd, I'm sorry.
What do you want?
I'm sorry.
My father's guilty.
He lied to me.
He lied to everybody.
I just left home.
I need you.
- You do?
- Everything else means nothing to me.
If I hurt you again, I'll die.
Hurt me again?
There's not a chance.
Don't worry about it.
I love you.
- What?
- I love you.
How many more times do I have to say it?
One more time would be nice.
[Quietly]
I love you.
Please. I love you.
Wait a minute.
Whoa.
One question.
Are you here 'cause you... need someone,
or 'cause you need me?
Forget it.
I don't care.
I need you.
[Sniffles]
I love you.
- [Man]
$75,000 fine and no jail.
- I can't give you that.
This guy's been rippin' off
grandma and grandpa
for 17 years.
He's been getting it
from every end.
I'd love to hear his story.
$100,000 fine
and three months?
125,000
and nine months.
I can accept that.
Course, they're gonna want
to turn the home over
to the state.
He'd like to start serving
immediately.
I can put that together.
Confirm this
with my office
and my client.
I'll push it past
my boss.
All right.
[Lloyd]
Just sleep.
I brought her all the way here.
She said she was gonna come,
and wouldn't get out of the car.
I thought it was important
to see you, because I know
that if you go somewhere...
and not deal with family stuff,
that you’re just gonna-
she's gonna... all- I just-
You going to England with her?
That's one of the things
I wanted to talk to you about.
- Are you?
- Am I going? Um-
Am I going to England?
I've thought about it
quite a bit,
and I've realized,
what I probably should do
is just carve out a goal,
find what I want to do
with my life— stuff I've been
avoiding in a big way.
I mean, Diane and I can wait
for each other, right?
What is she gonna do?
Is she just gonna run off
with some English guy?
There's no way.
Well, Lloyd, I admire you
for not hitching a ride.
You know, my daughter's
a lot different from you.
I know.
- She's very successful.
- I know.
She's very talented.
I know.
But then I reconsidered.
'Cause I figured, what I really
want to do with my life—
what I want to do for a living-
is I want to be
with your daughter.
I'm good at it.
You're not a permanent part of her life.
You're a distraction.
I'm the distraction
that's goin' with her
to England, sir.
You all right, sir? You okay?
[Loudly]
I'm incarcerated,
Lloyd!
I don't deserve to lose
my daughter over this.
I don't deserve
to have you
as my go-between,
and I can't for the life of me
figure out how she could choose
to champion mediocrity...
the way
she's learned to
around you!
I have a letter
from your daughter.
Do you want it?
[Quietly] Thank you..
[Man]
Visiting hours are now over.
All visitors must check out
with the attending officer.
[Paper Rustling]
Visiting hours are now over.
[Lloyd]
I don't know which version she sent.
[Mouthing Words]
-"You can't know the horrible
disappointment I feel."
-I know this part. Keep reading.
She can't still be angry at this.
It's gotta get better.
It does.
It does if it's the version signed
"I still can't help loving you."
It gets better.
Just her name.
Just knowing
a version like that exists-
that for a minute
she felt that and wrote,
"I still can't help loving you."
That's gotta be a good thing, right?
Gotta be a good thing.
Hello.
Hi.
I don't know what to say to you,
except good-bye.
[Mouths Word]
You could have told me the truth.
I'm so sorry.
I love you, Dad.
[Clicking Sound]
Write me.
[Man Singing Rock On Stereo]
♪ I could live without so much ♪
♪ I can die
without a clue ♪
♪ Sun keeps risin'
in the west ♪
♪ I keep on wakin'
fully confused ♪
♪♪ [Volume Increases]
♪ I never seen no mountain ♪
♪ Never swam no sea ♪
♪ City got me drownin' ♪
♪♪ [Drum Beats]
♪ I guess it's up to me ♪♪
[Jet Engine Whining]
[Hands Rubbing]
[Hydraulics Whirring]
Wing adjustments.
[Wind Roaring]
It's like a big roller coaster.
Everybody likes roller coasters, right?
Blink twice if you’re fine.
I'm fine.
Okay. Good.
This is all very normal.
[Engine Whining]
[Rattling, Squeaking]
Very standard
for a 747.
Okay.
[Whining Continues]
All right.
High-level airline safety tips:
If anything happens,
it'll happen the first
five minutes of the flight?
Okay.
So, when you hear that
smoking sign go ding, you know
everything's gonna be okay.
Good to know.
[Whining, Rattling Continues]
All right, I'm just gonna keep
talking until that ding happens,
which is going to be soon.
Okay.
All right. Personalized
flight gift from Corey: books,
cassettes, magazines, anything?
Not right now.
Thanks.
- How's it goin'?
- Mm-hmm.
[Clears Throat]
Nobody thought
we'd do this.
Nobody really thinks
it will work, do they?
No.
You just described
every great success story.
[Engine Whining]
[Hydraulics Whirring]
All right.
It's all right. It's all right.
I know.
[Rattling Resumes]
[Diane]
Where's the ding?
It's comin'.
Any second now.
[Sign Dings]
♪♪ [Pop, Medium Tempo]
[Woman]
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Looking at you tonight ♪
♪ Breathless at what I see ♪
♪ In your eyes there's someone ♪
♪ Come to carry me ♪
♪ Some never have a chance ♪
♪ Some throw their chance away ♪
♪ Now it's in my hands ♪
♪ I face it unafraid ♪
♪If we ever did one thing ♪
♪ That was right ♪
♪ We gave it all for love ♪
♪ Saved it all for love ♪
♪ Didn't we touch the fire above ♪
♪ And make music out of madness ♪
♪ We gave it all for love ♪
[Chorus]
♪ Whoa ♪
[Woman]
♪ Everything still to come ♪
♪ One thing will stay the same ♪
♪ We will heal each other♪
♪ And never turn away ♪
♪ To my lonely heart ♪
♪ You are my home ♪
♪ We gave it all for love ♪
♪ Saved it all for love ♪
♪ Didn't we touch the fire above ♪
♪ And make music out of madness ♪
♪ We gave it all ♪
♪ For love ♪
♪ To my lonely heart ♪
♪ You are my home ♪
[Chorus]
♪ Ah, love somebody ♪
♪ Didn't we touch the fire above ♪
[Chorus]
♪ To love somebody ♪
♪ It will carry us forever ♪
♪ Didn't we feel the fire for love ♪
♪ To love somebody ♪
♪ Tear down the walls for love ♪
♪ Didn't we do it all for love ♪
♪ To love somebody ♪
♪ And make music out of madness ♪
♪ Didn't we feel the fire for love ♪
♪ To love somebody ♪
♪ Tear down the walls for love ♪
♪ Didn't we do it all for love ♪
♪ To love somebody ♪
♪ And make music out of madness ♪
♪ We gave it all ♪
♪ We gave it all for love ♪
♪ Show me the way to your heart ♪
[Chorus]
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Show me the way to your heart ♪
♪ Show me the way ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Whoa ♪♪
[ © anoXmous
@ https://thepiratebay.sx/user/[qusawa]